THE CAPITAL JURY PROJECT RECORDS (APAP196) 1941-2011
M. E. Grenander Department of Special Collections and Archives
- CJP Phase III, 2004-2012; 3; 4
  - Administrative, 2004-2011; 3.2; 1
    - Texas Informed Consent*RESTRICTED*, 2010 January 25 (Box 1, Folder 17)
    - Transcript Review and Summarization Form: Laderrick Campbell *RESTRICTED*, Undated (Box 1, Folder 18)
    - The University at Albany Informed Consent Forms*RESTRICTED*, 2009 January; 2010 August; 2011 January (Box 1, Folder 19)
    - The University at Albany Informed Consent Statement, 2009 January 25 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Discs of Juror Interviews, 2007-2011; 3.3
    This Series is arranged Choronologically.
    This series contains the discs of the interviews with jurors and the interviewers. Much of the material is transcripts of trials and of juror interviews. The discs are restricted materials and all reproductions are prohibited.
    - Interview, 2007 January 8 (Disc 1, Dsic 1)
    - Interview, 2007 January 8 (Disc 2, Dsic 2)
    - CAP Transcripts, 2007 June 4 (Disc 3, Dsic 3)
    - CA Trials, 2007 December 3 (Disc 4, Dsic 4)
    - Delaware I, Capital - Transcripts, 2008 January 24 (Disc 5, Dsic 5)
    - Delaware II, Capital - Transcripts, 2008 January 24 (Disc 6, Dsic 6)
    - Transcript, 2008 January 24 (Disc 7, Dsic 7)
    - Capital Jury Project, 2008 June 1 (Disc 8, Dsic 8)
    - Capital Jury Project, 2008 June 3 (Disc 9, Dsic 9)
    - Capital Jury Project, 2008 June 5 (Disc 10, Dsic 10)
    - Capital Jury Project, 2008 June 7 (Disc 11, Dsic 11)
    - Oklahoma Material, 2008 June 22; 2008 August 19 (Disc 12, Dsic 12)
    - Capital Jury Project, 2008 July 19 (Disc 13, Dsic 13)
    - Interview, 2008 July 30 (Disc 14, Dsic 14)
    - Cap. Punishment, 2009 January 13 (Disc 15, Dsic 15)
    - Transcripts, 2009 January 27 (Disc 16, Dsic 16)
    - LWOP San Diego, CA, 2009 April 27 (Disc 17, Dsic 17)
    - Missouri Transcripts Disc 1, 2009 May 9 (Disc 18, Dsic 18)
    - Missouri Transcripts Disc 2, 2009 May 9 (Disc 19, Dsic 19)
    - Michael Anderson Voir Dire Transcripts, 2009 August 17 (Disc 20, Dsic 20)
    - State of Indiana v. Pruitt Disc 1, 2010 May 4 (Disc 21, Dsic 21)
    - State of Indiana v. Pruitt Disc 2, 2010 May 4 (Disc 22, Dsic 22)
    - Transcript (TX), 2010 June 2 (Disc 23, Dsic 23)
    - DE Data, 2010 june 17 (Disc 24, Dsic 24)
    - Interviews, 2010 June 30 (Disc 25, Dsic 25)
    - Interviews, 2010 June 30 (Disc 26, Dsic 26)
    - Interviews, 2010 June 30 (Disc 27, Dsic 27)
    - Interviews, 2010 June 30 (Disc 28, Dsic 28)
    - Interviews, 2010 June 30 (Disc 29, Dsic 29)
    - Interviews, 2010 June 30 (Disc 30, Dsic 30)
    - Interviews, 2010 June 30 (Disc 31, Dsic 31)
    - Interviews, 2010 August 10 (Disc 32, Dsic 32)
    - Interviews, 2010 August 19 (Disc 33, Dsic 33)
    - Interviews, 2010 August 19 (Disc 34, Dsic 34)
    - Interviews, 2010 August 19 (Disc 35, Dsic 35)
    - State of Indiana v. Price Transcript Review Forms Disc 1 of 4, 2010 August 26 (Disc 36, Dsic 36)
    - State of Indiana v. Price Audio Interviews Disc 2 of 4, 2010 August 26 (Disc 37, Dsic 37)
    - State of Indiana v. Price Audio Interviews Disc 3 of 4, 2010 August 26 (Disc 38, Dsic 38)
    - State of Indiana v. Price Transcript Disc 4 of 4, 2010 August 26 (Disc 39, Dsic 39)
    - Michael Anderson Trial Trial Transcript, 2010 August 26 (Disc 40, Dsic 40)
    - CJP Philadelphia Death Penalty Cases, 2010 September 13 (Disc 41, Dsic 41)
    - CJP Philadelphia Death Penalty Cases, 2010 September 13 (Disc 42, Dsic 42)
    - Transcript Review, 2010 September 20 (Disc 43, Dsic 43)
    - Transcripts and Other Materials, 2010 September 20 (Disc 44, Dsic 44)
    - Interviews, 2010 December 15 (Disc 45, Dsic 45)
    - State of Louisiana v. Gerald Bordelon Compiled Interview Audio, 2011 August 8 (Disc 46, Dsic 46)
    - State of Louisiana v. Gerald Bordelon Case Level Data, 2011 August 8 (Disc 47, Dsic 47)
    - CJP Oklahoma Cases, 2011 October 13 (Disc 48, Dsic 48)
    - Various Interviews, 2011 November 2 (Disc 49, Dsic 49)
    - State of Indiana v. Stroud Audio Interviews Disc 1 of 2, 2011 November 25 (Disc 50, Dsic 50)
    - State of Indiana v. Stroud Audio Interviews Disc 2 of 2, 2011 November 25 (Disc 51, Dsic 51)
    - State of Indiana v. Dickens Trial Transcript and Audio Interviews Disc 1 of 2, 2011 November 25 (Disc 52, Dsic 52)
    - State of Indiana v. Dickens Trial Transcript and Audio Interviews Disc 2 of 2, 2011 November 25 (Disc 53, Dsic 53)
    - CJP Pennsylvania, 2011 November 26 (Disc 54, Dsic 54)
    - CJP Pennsylvania, 2011 November 26 (Disc 55, Dsic 55)
- William J. Bowers, 1974-2003; 4; no cubic ft.
  Correspondence and Clemency Work are arranged alphabetically and Scholarship and Teaching are arranged chronologically.
  Principal Investigator of the CJP is William J. Bowers (Ph.D., Columbia University, 1966). He was Principal Research Scientist in the School of Criminal Justice, University at Albany, as well as formerly at Northeastern University. For his research on capital punishment, in 2000 Dr. Bowers received the American Society of Criminology's August Vollmer Award for outstanding contributions in applied criminology. This series contains correspondence with other noted criminal justice scholars and activists, Clemency applications, and general teaching materials including case transcripts while Dr. Bowers was a professor.
  - Correspondence, 1974-2003; 4.1; 1.4
    Arragned Alphabetically.
    This series contains Professor Bowers's personal correspondence with other noted Death Penalty scholars and activists.
    - Correspondence - 1992 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence - 1995 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence - 1996 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence - Answered Requests, 1992 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence - Baldus. David C., 2002 October 8 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence - Baldus. David C., Undated (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence - Bandes, Susan, Undated (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Correspondence - Beatrix, Simon, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - Correspondence - Bedau, Hugs A., 1994; 1999; Undated (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - Correspondence - Berman, Douglas, Undated (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - Correspondence - Beth H. Israel, 2000 October 26 (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - Correspondence - Bienen, Leigh, 1994; 1995 (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - Correspondence - Bruderhof Foundation, Undated (Box 1, Folder 13)
    - Correspondence - Buchanan, Pat, Undated (Box 1, Folder 14)
    - Correspondence - Buckle, Len and Susan, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 15)
    - Correspondence - Costanzo, Sally and Mark, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 16)
    - Correspondence - Dieter, Richard, 1993; 1994 (Box 1, Folder 17)
    - Correspondence - Duran, Dennis, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 18)
    - Correspondence - Dzugan, William S., 1994 (Box 1, Folder 19)
    - Correspondence - Ehrlich, Issac, 1974-1977; 1996 (Box 1, Folder 20)
    - Correspondence - Eisenberg, Ted, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 21)
    - Correspondence - Espy M. Watt, 1984-1986; 1988 (Box 1, Folder 22)
    - Correspondence - Espy M. Watt, 1987 (Box 1, Folder 23)
    - Correspondence - Espy M. Watt, 1991-1997 (Box 1, Folder 24)
    - Correspondence - Farrel, Michael, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 25)
    - Correspondence - Faxes Received, 1994; 1995; 1996 (Box 1, Folder 26)
    - Correspondence - Fogalia, Wanda D. about the Criminal Law Bulletin Symposium, 2002 November 12 (Box 1, Folder 27)
    - Correspondence - Fox, James Alan, 1991 (Box 1, Folder 28)
    - Correspondence - Frolich, William A., 2001 September 14 (Box 1, Folder 29)
    - Correspondence - General, Undated (Box 1, Folder 30)
    - Correspondence - General, 1996; Undated (Box 1, Folder 31)
    - Correspondence - Gradess, Jonathan, 1991; 1994; 1995 (Box 1, Folder 32)
    - Correspondence - Greene, Edith, 1993 - 1994 (Box 1, Folder 33)
    - Correspondence - Gross, Samuel R., 2002 (Box 1, Folder 34)
    - Correspondence - Hinebaugh, F. Lee, 2005 April 18 (Box 1, Folder 35)
    - Correspondence - Hoffman, Joseph, 1994 May 6 (Box 1, Folder 36)
    - Correspondence - Israel, Beth, 2000 (Box 1, Folder 37)
    - Correspondence - Kurber, Lisa and Steele, Tracy, Undated (Box 1, Folder 38)
    - Correspondence - Laub, John, 1994 - 1996 (Box 1, Folder 39)
    - Correspondence - Long, Walter, Undated (Box 1, Folder 40)
    - Correspondence - LSR Reviews, 1999 (Box 1, Folder 41)
    - Correspondence - Luginbuhl, James, 1993 - 1994 (Box 1, Folder 42)
    - Correspondence - Lynch, Mona, Undated (Box 1, Folder 43)
    - Correspondence - Marquart, Jim and Jordan Steiker, 1994 - 1995 (Box 1, Folder 44)
    - Correspondence - Mello, Michael, 1995 November 13 (Box 1, Folder 45)
    - Correspondence - Missouri, 1992; 1993 (Box 1, Folder 46)
    - Correspondence - Mulroy, Steve, 2002 December 19 (Box 1, Folder 47)
    - Correspondence - Murphy, James, Undated (Box 1, Folder 48)
    - Correspondence - Murray, Chris, 2003 June 4 (Box 1, Folder 49)
    - Correspondence - Myers, Laura, 1992 June 15 (Box 1, Folder 50)
    - Correspondence - Nathanson, Steve, 2001 June 4 (Box 1, Folder 51)
    - Correspondence - Northeastern University Assorted, 1999 (Box 1, Folder 52)
    - Correspondence - Northeastern University Press, 1985 (Box 1, Folder 53)
    - Correspondence - Parker, Paul, 2000 November 15 (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence - Prejean, Helen, 1994; Undated (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence - Price, Melynda, Undated (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence - Rosenbaum, Dennis C., 1992 (Box 2, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence - Ross, Michael, 1994 - 1997 (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence - Russel, Kathryn, 1993 February - August (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence - Sallings, Deborah, 1994 (Box 2, Folder 7)
    - Correspondence - Sandys, Marla, 1992-1996 (Box 2, Folder 8)
    - Correspondence - Sarat, Austin, 1992 - 1994 (Box 2, Folder 9)
    - Correspondence - Sheppard, Sam, 1999 (Box 2, Folder 10)
    - Correspondence - Sloan, Virginia, 2001 (Box 2, Folder 11)
    - Correspondence - Sundby, Scott, 1993 - 1996 (Box 2, Folder 12)
    - Correspondence - Steiker, Jordan, 1995 April 24 (Box 2, Folder 13)
    - Correspondence - The Center on Crime, Communities of Culture, Undated (Box 2, Folder 14)
    - Correspondence - Thompson, Michael, 2002 September 10 (Box 2, Folder 15)
    - Correspondence - Tull, Captian, Undated (Box 2, Folder 16)
    - Correspondence - Vandiver, Margaret, 1992 - 1997 (Box 2, Folder 17)
    - Correspondence - Villarosa, Lori (Mott Foundation), 1999 August 25 (Box 2, Folder 18)
    - Correspondence - Waldo, Gordon, 1994 April - August (Box 2, Folder 19)
    - Correspondence - Wierschem, Joe, 1992; 1993 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Clemency Work, 1993-2001; 4.2; 1.8
    This series contains Clemency Petitions collected from inmates from across the nation.
    - Addendum to Application for Commutation of a Sentence of Death- Bannister, Alan Jeffrey, Undated (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Application for Executive Clemency and/or Commutation of a Sentence of Death- Griffin, Larry, Undated (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Application for Executive Clemency- Kilgore Bruce, 1999 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - An Application for Executive Clemency for Lonnie Weeks, Jr., 2000 March 10 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Application for Executive Clemency- Schlup,Lloyd Eugene Jr., Undated (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Application for Executive Clemency in matter of Young, Kevin D., 2000 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - An Application for Executive Clemency for Wright, Dwayne A., 1998 October 13 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Application for a Reprieve from, or Commutation of, A Sentence of Death- Bolder, Martsay, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - Application for Reprieve from, or Commutation or, A Sentence of Death- Polland, Roosevelt Jr. (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - Application + Request for a Hearing and a Reprieve from or Commutation of a Sentence of Death - Lavette, Anthony J. JR, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - Application + Request for a Hearing and a Reprieve from or Commutation of a Sentence of Death - Preston, Elvoy, 1998 (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - The Arca Foundation Grant letters and Abstract, 2001 (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - Before the Board of Pardon + Parole State of Oklahoma - A Plea for Clemency from John W. Castro, Sr., Undated (Box 1, Folder 13)
    - Capital Defendant's Clemency Inventory + Notes, 2000; Undated (Box 1, Folder 14)
    - "The Clemency Alternative" Burnett, Cathleen Proposal, 1999 (Box 1, Folder 15)
    - Clemency Attorney Responses, 2002 (Box 1, Folder 16)
    - Clemency Atty's, Undated (Box 1, Folder 17)
    - Clemency Hearing of Dion Athanasius Smallwood, 2000 December 4 (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - Clemency Hearing of Dion Athanasius Smallwood, 2000 December 4 (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - Clemency Petition- Richardson, Miguel, 2001; 2002; Undated (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - Clemency Petitions Status of Defendents, Undated (Box 2, Folder 4)
    - A Compelling Case for Mercy: The Petition for Executive Clemency for Sellers, Sean Richard, 1998; 1999; Undated (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - Exhibits in Support of Application for Commutation of a Sentence of Death- Blair,Walter J., Undated (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - Petition for Clemency before the Oklahoma Board of Pardon and Parole- Smallwood, Dion A., 2000 December 4 (Box 2, Folder 7)
    - Petition for Clemency- Bolick, William T., 1997 (Box 2, Folder 8)
    - Petition for Clemency- Malone, Kelvin, 1999 (Box 3, Folder 1)
    - Petition for Executive Clemency and/or Commutation of a Death Sentence, 2000 (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - Petition for Executive Clemency- Eaton, Dennis W., Undated (Box 3, Folder 3)
    - Petition for a Recommendation of a Reprieve of Execution and Pardon, or Alternatively, a Conditional Pardon or Commutation of Death Sentence- Graham, Gary, 2000 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Scholarship and Teaching, 1979-2003; 4.3; 3.4
    Arranged Chronogolically.
    The Scholarship and Teaching series represents Professor Bowers scholarly interests and materials used in his classes. The archivist kept the materials together as that was how they were donated.
    - Northeastern University Spivack Fellowship- Nomination Support, 1979 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Northeastern University Spivack Fellowship Review for William J. Bowers, 1979 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Northeastern Alumni Magazine, 1983 may- june (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Kansas Citizens Survery, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - NSF Form 1359, 1998 october (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Northeastern University Press Book Contract and Publishing Information, 1999 december 1; undated (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Atkins V. Virginia (1999), 2000 august 9 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Beathard V. Johnson, 2000 august 2 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - Beets v. Johnson, 2000 august 2 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - Boyd v. Johnson, 2000 august 2 (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - Brooks v. Texas, 2000 august 2 (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - Burdine v. Johnson, 2000 august 2 (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - Bramblett v. Commonwealth of Virginia, 2000 august 2 (Box 1, Folder 13)
    - Busby v. Texas, 2000 august 2 (Box 1, Folder 14)
    - California v. Carpenter, 2000 august 2 (Box 1, Folder 15)
    - California v. Hart, 2000 august 2 (Box 1, Folder 16)
    - California v. Hayes, 2000 august 2 (Box 1, Folder 17)
    - California v. Smithey, 2000 august 2 (Box 1, Folder 18)
    - California v. Welch, 2000 august 2 (Box 1, Folder 19)
    - Cathey v. Texas, 2000 august 2 (Box 1, Folder 20)
    - Cherrix v. Virginia, 2000 august 2 (Box 1, Folder 21)
    - Correspondence Regarding "National Committee to Prevent Wrongful Executions", 2001 January 31 (Box 1, Folder 22)
    - Correspondence Regarding "National Committee to Prevent Wrongful Executions", 2000 August 2 (Box 1, Folder 23)
    - Etheridge v. Johnson, 2000 August 2 (Box 1, Folder 24)
    - Faulder v. Johnson, 2000 August 2 (Box 1, Folder 25)
    - Felder v. Johnson, 2000 August 2 (Box 1, Folder 26)
    - Fuentes v. State, 2000 August 2 (Box 1, Folder 27)
    - Graham v. Angelone, 2000 August 2 (Box 1, Folder 28)
    - Hedrick v. Commonwealth of Virginia, 2000 August 2 (Box 1, Folder 29)
    - Hicks v. Johnson, 2000 August 2 (Box 1, Folder 30)
    - Hinojasa v. Texas, 2000 August 2 (Box 1, Folder 31)
    - Hughes v. Johnson, 2000 August 2 (Box 1, Folder 32)
    - In re Sanders, 21 Cal. 4th 697 (1999), 2000 August 2 (Box 1, Folder 33)
    - Jackson v. Johnson, 2000 August 2 (Box 1, Folder 34)
    - Jones v. US, 2000 August 2 (Box 1, Folder 35)
    - Kitchens v. Johnson, 2000 August 2 (Box 1, Folder 36)
    - Knighten v. State of Texas, 2000 August 2 (Box 1, Folder 37)
    - Knox v. Johnson, 2000 August 2 (Box 1, Folder 38)
    - Kutzner v. Texas, 2000 August 2 (Box 1, Folder 39)
    - Ladd v. State of Texas, 2000 August 2 (Box 1, Folder 40)
    - Lamb v. Johnson, 2000 August 2 (Box 1, Folder 41)
    - Maldonado v. Texas, 2000 August 2 (Box 1, Folder 42)
    - Malone v. Calderon, 2000 August 2 (Box 1, Folder 43)
    - Malone v. Superior Court, 2000 August 2 (Box 1, Folder 44)
    - Mickens v. Greene, 2000 August 2 (Box 1, Folder 45)
    - Millsap v. Superior Court, 2000 August 2 (Box 1, Folder 46)
    - Payne v. Commonwealth of Virginia, 2000 August 2 (Box 1, Folder 47)
    - Rosales v. Texas, 2000 August 2 (Box 1, Folder 48)
    - Shields v. Johnson, 2000 August 2 (Box 1, Folder 49)
    - Siripongs v. Calderon, 2000 August 2 (Box 1, Folder 50)
    - Townsel v. Superior Court, 2000 August 2 (Box 1, Folder 51)
    - Trevino v. Texas, 2000 August 2 (Box 1, Folder 52)
    - Vinson v. Commonwealth of Virginia, 2000 August 2 (Box 1, Folder 53)
    - Williams v. Angelone, 2000 August 2 (Box 1, Folder 54)
    - Williams v. Calderon, 2000 August 2 (Box 1, Folder 55)
    - Alve v. Small, 2000 August 21 (Box 1, Folder 56)
    - Babbitt v. Woodford, 2000 August 21 (Box 1, Folder 57)
    - Banks v. Horn, 2000 August 21 (Box 1, Folder 58)
    - Buehl v. Vaughn, 2000 August 21 (Box 1, Folder 59)
    - Burkett v. Angelone, 2000 August 21 (Box 1, Folder 60)
    - Chamberlain v. Texas, 2000 August 21 (Box 1, Folder 61)
    - Chichester v. Taylor, 2000 August 21 (Box 1, Folder 62)
    - Chicester v. Taylor, 2000 August 21 (Box 1, Folder 63)
    - Correspondence Regarding "National Committee to Prevent Wrongful Executions", 2000 August 21 (Box 1, Folder 64)
    - Graham v. Johnson, 2000 August 21 (Box 1, Folder 65)
    - Guidry v. Texas, 2000 August 21 (Box 1, Folder 66)
    - Ibarra v. Texas, 2000 August 21 (Box 1, Folder 67)
    - In Re Cudjo, 2000 August 21 (Box 1, Folder 68)
    - In Re Hamilton, 2000 August 21 (Box 1, Folder 69)
    - Jackson v. Texas, 2000 August 21 (Box 1, Folder 70)
    - Jenkins v. Angelone, 2000 August 21 (Box 1, Folder 71)
    - Johnson v. Tennessee, 2000 August 21 (Box 1, Folder 72)
    - Joseph v. Angelone, 2000 August 21 (Box 1, Folder 73)
    - King v. Tennessee, 2000 August 21 (Box 1, Folder 74)
    - Medina v. Texas, 2000 August 21 (Box 1, Folder 75)
    - Pennsylvania v. Beasley, 2000 August 21 (Box 1, Folder 76)
    - Pennsylvania v. Jacobs, 2000 August 21 (Box 1, Folder 77)
    - Pennsylvania v. Koehler, 2000 August 21 (Box 1, Folder 78)
    - Pennsylvania v. Laird, 2000 August 21 (Box 1, Folder 79)
    - Pennsylvania v. Porter, 2000 August 21 (Box 1, Folder 80)
    - Pennsylvania v. Puksar, 2000 August 21 (Box 1, Folder 81)
    - Pennsylvania v. Rollins, 2000 August 21 (Box 1, Folder 82)
    - Prystash v. Texas, 2000 August 21 (Box 1, Folder 83)
    - Swann v. Taylor, 2000 August 21 (Box 1, Folder 84)
    - Trevino v. Johnson, 2000 August 21 (Box 1, Folder 85)
    - United States v. Garza, 2000 August 21 (Box 1, Folder 86)
    - Yarbrough v. Virginia, 2000 August 21 (Box 1, Folder 87)
    - Wilson v. Texas, 2000 August 21 (Box 1, Folder 88)
    - Weeks v. Angelone, 2000 August 21 (Box 1, Folder 89)
    - Moreland v. Scott, 2000 August 25 (Box 1, Folder 90)
    - Benefiel v. State, 716 N.E. 2d 906 ( Ind. 1999), 2000 October 2 (Box 1, Folder 91)
    - Black v. Tennessee, 120 S.Ct. 1249 (2000), 2000 October 2 (Box 1, Folder 92)
    - Clark v. State of Texas ( 1999), 2000 October 2 (Box 1, Folder 93)
    - 512 Pa. 298 (1986) Com. V. Fahy, 2000 October 2 (Box 1, Folder 94)
    - 557 Pa/ 531, Com. V. Faulkner, 2000 October 2 (Box 1, Folder 95)
    - Com. V. Fisher, 527 Pa. 345 ( 1991), 2000 October 2 (Box 1, Folder 96)
    - 120 S. Ct. 1178 (2000) Com. v. Hackett, 2000 October 2 (Box 1, Folder 97)
    - Com. v. Mason, 2000 October 2 (Box 1, Folder 98)
    - Commonwealth v. proctor, 526 Pa. 246 (1991), 2000 October 2 (Box 1, Folder 99)
    - Com. V. Thompson, 2000 October 2 (Box 1, Folder 100)
    - Correspondence Regarding "National Committee to Prevent Wrongful Executions", 2000 October 2 (Box 1, Folder 101)
    - Crane v. Johnson ( 1999), 2000 October 2 (Box 1, Folder 102)
    - Dewberry v. Texas, 2000 October 2 (Box 1, Folder 103)
    - Douglas v. Pennsylvania, 120 C.Ct. 2220 (2000), 2000 October 2 (Box 1, Folder 104)
    - Dye v. Indiana, 2000 October 2 (Box 1, Folder 105)
    - Keaton v. Pennsylvania 120 S. Ct. 1180 (2000), 2000 October 2 (Box 1, Folder 106)
    - McCormick v. Tennessee, 494 U.S. 1039 (1990), 2000 October 2 (Box 1, Folder 107)
    - Orbe v. Commonwealth, 258 Va. 390 ( 1990), 2000 October 2 (Box 1, Folder 108)
    - Owens v. Tennessee ( 1994), 2000 October 2 (Box 1, Folder 109)
    - Ramdass v. Angelone, 2000 October 2 (Box 1, Folder 110)
    - Royal v. Taylor, 2000 October 2 (Box 1, Folder 111)
    - 519 U.S. 855 (1996) Stevens v. Pennsylvania, 2000 October 2 (Box 1, Folder 112)
    - Strickler v. Greene, 2000 October 2 (Box 1, Folder 113)
    - Thomas v. Taylor, 2000 October 2 (Box 1, Folder 114)
    - Tennessee v. Bondurant, 2000 October 2 (Box 1, Folder 115)
    - Tennessee v. Carruthers, 2000 October 2 (Box 1, Folder 116)
    - Tennessee v. Carter, 2000 October 2 (Box 1, Folder 117)
    - Tennessee v. Henderson, 2000 October 2 (Box 1, Folder 118)
    - Tennessee v. Keen ( 1999), 2000 October 2 (Box 1, Folder 119)
    - 727 S.W. 2d. 490 (1987) Tennessee v. McNish, 2000 October 2 (Box 1, Folder 120)
    - Tennessee v. Miller, 771 S.W. 2d 401 ( 1989), 2000 October 2 (Box 1, Folder 121)
    - Walker v. Com., 2000 October 2 (Box 1, Folder 122)
    - U.S. v. Butler, 2000 October 2 (Box 1, Folder 123)
    - U.S. v. Carpenter, 2000 October 2 (Box 1, Folder 124)
    - Williams v. Taylor, 2000 October 2 (Box 1, Folder 125)
    - Thesis Proposal Kristie Faller, 2000 October (Box 1, Folder 126)
    - Student Papers, 2000; Undated (Box 1, Folder 127)
    - 1999 U.S. Dist. Lexis 7530 ( E.D. Pa. 1999) Appel v. Horn, 2001 January 10 (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - Azania v. Bechert, 2001 January 10 (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - Benefiel v. Indiana, 2001 January 10 (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - Blystone v. Pennsylvania, 2001 January 10 (Box 2, Folder 4)
    - Coker v. Tennessee, 2001 January 10 (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - Commonwealth v. Breakiron, 2001 January 10 (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - Commonwealth of Pennsylvania v. Holland, 2001 January 10 (Box 2, Folder 7)
    - Commonwealth v. Holloway, 2001 January 10 (Box 2, Folder 8)
    - Commonwealth of Pennsylvania v. Lopez, 2001 January 10 (Box 2, Folder 9)
    - Commonwealth of Pennsylvania v. Murphy, 2001 January 10 (Box 2, Folder 10)
    - Commonwealth of Pennsylvania v. Ragen, 2001 January 10 (Box 2, Folder 11)
    - Commonwealth of Pennsylvania v. Romero, 2001 January 10 (Box 2, Folder 12)
    - Commonwealth of Pennsylvania v. Small, 2001 January 10 (Box 2, Folder 13)
    - Commonwealth of Pennsylvania v. Wallance, 2001 January 10 (Box 2, Folder 14)
    - Commonwealth of Pennsylvania v. White, 2001 January 10 (Box 2, Folder 15)
    - Commonwealth of Pennsylvania v. Yanis, 2001 January 10 (Box 2, Folder 16)
    - Commonwealth of Pennsylvania v. Young, 2001 January 10 (Box 2, Folder 17)
    - Calderon v. McDowell, 2001 January 10 (Box 2, Folder 18)
    - Carson v. Pennsylvania, 2001 January 10 (Box 2, Folder 19)
    - Conner v. State of Indiana, 2001 January 10 (Box 2, Folder 20)